[{"answer": "THE LIFE AND TIMES OF JESUS OF NAZARETH\": Well, to be clear, I am a scholar of religions with four degrees including one in the New Testament and fluency in biblical Greek, who has been studying the origins of Christianity for two decades who also just happens to be a Muslim.", "docId": "130729pmt", "aSentId": 14, "question": "You're a Muslim, so why did you write a book about the founder of Christianity?", "qSentId": 13}, {"answer": "Well, I don't think it's the first time she's definitely going to run.", "docId": "130729pmt", "aSentId": 36, "question": "Do you think that?", "qSentId": 35}, {"answer": "Well, obviously the answer is yes, it brings it all back.", "docId": "130729pmt", "aSentId": 52, "question": "It sort of -- it brings it all back, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 51}, {"answer": "I do see that distinction.", "docId": "130729pmt", "aSentId": 100, "question": "In Snowden's case, you know, to be fair to the guy, he can try and be quite judicious in what he put out there, do you see that distinction?", "qSentId": 99}, {"answer": "That's the point.", "docId": "130729pmt", "aSentId": 106, "question": "But where do you draw the line there particularly in a modern era?", "qSentId": 105}, {"answer": "Frankly, yes.", "docId": "130729pmt", "aSentId": 127, "question": "Badge of honor, Dan?", "qSentId": 126}, {"answer": "Apparently so.", "docId": "130729pmt", "aSentId": 148, "question": "Was that true?", "qSentId": 147}, {"answer": "No, I don't think so.", "docId": "130729pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "(INAUDIBLE), isn't it?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "Absolutely, Piers.", "docId": "130729pmt", "aSentId": 197, "question": "Is this basically going on in every city in America?", "qSentId": 196}, {"answer": "I think his son turned out to be a way better man than this coward was.", "docId": "130729pmt", "aSentId": 214, "question": "I assume you agree with that, John?", "qSentId": 213}, {"answer": "Well, to be clear, I am a scholar of religions with four degrees, including one in the New Testament and fluency in biblical Greek who has been studying the origins of Christianity for two decades, who also just happens to be a Muslim.", "docId": "130729pmt", "aSentId": 226, "question": "Now I want to be clear, you're a Muslim, so why did you write a book about the founder of Christianity?", "qSentId": 225}, {"answer": "Because it's my job as an academic.", "docId": "130729pmt", "aSentId": 231, "question": "But it still begs the question, though -- it still begs the question, why would you be interested in the founder of Christianity?", "qSentId": 230}, {"answer": "Well, look, I mean, truly I was kind of embarrassed.", "docId": "130729pmt", "aSentId": 239, "question": "And, Reza, I mean, what were you thinking as that interviewer was asking those ridiculous questions?", "qSentId": 238}, {"answer": "Well, the book is a historical biography of a man named Jesus of Nazareth.", "docId": "130729pmt", "aSentId": 250, "question": "What is the premise of the book and what is the conclusion that you reached?", "qSentId": 249}, {"answer": "I think for sure.", "docId": "130729pmt", "aSentId": 257, "question": "Taking the FOX interview as the basis for this next question, but do you think it would be helpful generally if more Muslims read more about Christianity, more Christians read more about the Muslim faith?", "qSentId": 256}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130729pmt", "aSentId": 270, "question": "It was quite interesting, isn't it?", "qSentId": 269}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, the first thing to point out is the purpose of the fundraiser was not just to buy a gun.", "docId": "130729pmt", "aSentId": 298, "question": "Why do you want George Zimmerman to have a gun so badly?", "qSentId": 297}, {"answer": "I'm not aware of any threats against Mr. Martin's family for the fact that Mr. Zimmerman was acquitted.", "docId": "130729pmt", "aSentId": 302, "question": "Have you thought about their security going forward?", "qSentId": 301}, {"answer": "Well, if we're the ones that supplied the gun -- and again remember, we provided money, not a gun.", "docId": "130729pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "Where does that leave you if you're the one that supplied the gun?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "If he's acting legally in self-defense again, absolutely.", "docId": "130729pmt", "aSentId": 318, "question": "You will sleep soundly if he did that again?", "qSentId": 317}, {"answer": "Well, again, two different levels of government review have found no fault with Mr. Zimmerman's actions.", "docId": "130729pmt", "aSentId": 320, "question": "And at what point does he have to take responsibility for not pursuing, some would say stalking unarmed teenagers who are walking home?", "qSentId": 319}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, we can go through all the hypotheticals that you'd like to go through.", "docId": "130729pmt", "aSentId": 326, "question": "But what if he then does it again?", "qSentId": 325}, {"answer": "Well, the United States did not have a duty to retrieve in its laws in -- in most states until the 1920s, the 1930s.", "docId": "130729pmt", "aSentId": 341, "question": "What is your view of Florida's stand-your-ground law, and indeed a law that many other states have embraced?", "qSentId": 340}, {"answer": "Oh, the taking of a human life is the last resort -- morally, religiously, ethically and legally.", "docId": "130729pmt", "aSentId": 352, "question": "So just to clarify, you don't think there should ever really be a situation where you have a duty to retreat?", "qSentId": 351}, {"answer": "Have you ever thought that you could reduce the taking of human lives if you reduce the number of guns.", "docId": "130729pmt", "aSentId": 359, "question": "That's always the first step in a self-defense case is can you avoid the taking of the human life?", "qSentId": 358}, {"answer": "Oh, certainly, as a prosecutor for over 12 years, as someone who has been a court-appointed counsel in murders, rapes, kidnappings, that thought has crossed my mind.", "docId": "130729pmt", "aSentId": 361, "question": "Has that thought process ever crossed your mind?", "qSentId": 360}, {"answer": "You can write all the laws you want down on a piece of paper.", "docId": "130729pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "What do you mean by that?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "Countries are based upon the culture of the country.", "docId": "130729pmt", "aSentId": 379, "question": "How do you explain that if your theory is it makes no difference?", "qSentId": 378}, {"answer": "Well, I -- I mean, there are a lot of people -- I'm not saying he's one of them who have an economic stake in making sure that the gun industry not only survives, but thrives.", "docId": "130729pmt", "aSentId": 407, "question": "How do you change that thinking?", "qSentId": 406}, {"answer": "Yes, but we've drawn a line at the wrong place.", "docId": "130729pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "But as Dan Rather said, doesn't there have to be some line drawn as to what kind of information people can put into the public domain?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "LLRED: I would translate what Alan just said so eloquently like this, that we really need to change it on a legislative level.", "docId": "130729pmt", "aSentId": 441, "question": "Gloria, what -- what do you think?", "qSentId": 440}, {"answer": "Well, at this point, it might be Elliot Spitzer.", "docId": "130729pmt", "aSentId": 485, "question": "And of these three men, who has the greater chance of survival?", "qSentId": 484}, {"answer": "Well, one thing that should be pointed out is all three of these people are progressive, liberal, civil rights advocates, supporters of women rights.", "docId": "130729pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "What is the difference really between what he used to get up to and what Anthony Weiner gets up to other than Weiner never actually met these women?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, I want to differ with Alan on the fact that the allegation that all of the women were voluntarily involved in this, my client, Ginger Lee (ph), did not send any sext to Anthony Weiner and nor did she send any photos of herself.", "docId": "130729pmt", "aSentId": 510, "question": "...yes, on that point, though, that Alan made about the difference between JFK, say, and Anthony Weiner, what is the difference?", "qSentId": 509}, {"answer": "We know now but we didn't know then.", "docId": "130729pmt", "aSentId": 526, "question": "...we know now, don't we?", "qSentId": 525}, {"answer": "I agree.", "docId": "130729pmt", "aSentId": 531, "question": "Gloria?", "qSentId": 530}]